What should I do?
どうすんの?
What are you doing today?
どうすんの、今日だった?
Hey, what are you doing?
なあ、どうすんの?
Hey.
なあ
What should I do?
どうすんの?
What are you going to do about that?
あれどうすんの?
No, it's disgusting.
いいや、むちんやわなんで
Hey, is it too late now?
なあ、もう、今更ちゃう?
Ah.
な あ
Want to check it out here?
ここでチェックしてみる?
Are you cleaning it up a bit?
ちょっと綺麗に洗っているか
No, in the next room.
違う、隣の部屋で
I'm sleeping in this seat too.
この座席でも寝てるね
Hey.
なあ
I can't speak with that kind of voice.
ああいう声じゃ喋れんぞ
Look, it's for this one.
ほら、こっち向けや
I can't speak with that kind of voice.
ああいう声じゃ喋れんね
Why don't you have my phone?
なんで俺の携帯持ってないの?
It's okay to take that much
そんなに取んでもいいや
yeah.
ん
Do you want your mother to tell you?
お 母さんに言ってもらう?
Aren't you crying too much?
お泣きすぎない?
If you do it.
やったらよ
By the way, if Nashiote-kun comes out today,
間、なしおてくんが今日出てきたら、
I think a different child came down.
違う子降りてきたと思うなんで
You'll be seen.
見られてまうわけ
Let's do it.
してみや
Let's prioritize.
優先してみや
what are you doing?
何してるの?
How do you do it?
どうやってやってるの?
I'm extremely sensitive, so I keep attacking this area.
すごい敏感なんで、ずーっとここ攻めてるんすよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよ
Should I go with my dad?
これだとお父さんと行こうか?
Hey.
なあ
I don't like it.
嫌です
Shall we go?
行こうか?
Shall we go now?
今から行く?
I don't like it.
嫌です
why?
なんで?
Let's go to mom.
お母さんに行こうよ
Let's go get some coffee.
コーヒーかに行こうよ
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
なあ
let's go.
行こう
If you do this, let's go to my mom for a moment.
こうすればちょっとお母さんに行こう
Let me take you for a moment.
ちょっと連れて行きましょう
I'll take a quick look and see if I can find it.
俺もさっくっと見て、さっさといるかも
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Look, it's obstructed.
ふさいとも、ほら
I'm full of motivation today.
俺、今日はやる気満々やけど
Look, Mr. Ren, it's only after you turn towards me.
ほら、連さん、こっち向いてからだこと
I'm sending it to my mom.
お母さんに送ってるから
Mom, what should I say your name?
お母さん、名前何て言おう?
What should I say your name?
名前何て言おう?
tell me.
教えて
I don't like it.
嫌です
Hint.
ヒント
If you told me your name, I would edit it for you today.
名前教えてくれたら、今日の編集もあったんで
Open it again.
また開いて
Do it all.
やるべて
Mom, what should I do?
お母さん、どうしようか
This room is very hot.
このお部屋はめっちゃ暑いですからね
Let's stop taking a bath together later.
あとで一緒に風呂はやめよう
Yes, for this one.
はい、こっち向け
This way.
こっち
Walk carefully.
しっかりと歩いて
feeling
気 持 ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Do it all.
やるべて
over there.
あ、そこ
It feels good there.
そこ、そこ気持ちいい
Ah, I'll go again.
あ、また行っちゃうよ
Ah, I'll go.
あ、行くわ
Go, go, go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く、行く、行く
I'll go again.
また行くわ
Do it, sit down.
やるべて、座って
Do it all.
やるべて
Just open the bento mark.
ちょっと弁当マーク開けてごらん
How long will you have the money?
いつまでのお金持ってこんの?
What do you do if you exceed that?
それをすぎたらどうする?
I guess it's already too late.
てかもうすぎてるやんか
Yeah, I'll tell you about it now.
うん、 今からお消息するわ
Shall we go out?
外行こっか
Come on.
おいで
Hey, stand up and come on.
おい、立ち上がってほら、おいで
Yes, I'll do my best.
はい、やるべて行くよ
Well then, just go.
じゃあ、そんと行っちゃいで
Oh, let's go, come on.
あ、行こう、はい、おいで
Hominicocca.
ホミニコッカ
I don't like it.
嫌です
What should I do?
どうする?
Yes, get the toys out.
はい、おもちゃ出ろよ
Do you like it?
お好き?
Keep up with the toys.
おもちゃついていけ